<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The M47r1x</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The M47r1x</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>(c) Zion</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Grayhat -&gt; Secarmy CTF :: The Unintended Way</title>
      <link>/posts/secarmy-unintended-ctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/secarmy-unintended-ctf/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time, a CTF was held. There were many ways to solve it, though none knew that one was The Unintended Way. Although, it does sound pretty unconventional and sad that in a CTF where you explore all the paths and explore wild possibilities, one of them was tagged as unintended and thus, invalid.
Without further ado, let&amp;rsquo;s discover what it was.
The CTF The CTF was hosted on vulnhub, you were provided with an ova virtualbox image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multiple connections - Faster internet ?</title>
      <link>/posts/multi-net/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/multi-net/</guid>
      <description>Neo, we must find a faster link, connection to the Matrix is congested. Hurry !
 Kernel supports a magical module, called bonding
 Bonding: methods of combining (aggregating) multiple network connections in parallel in order to increase throughput
 This seems to be exactly what I need. I&amp;rsquo;ve two ISPs , let&amp;rsquo;s go ahead and connect two of my android devices via USB Tethering and bond both the connections and enter into the matrix!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Neo  I know you&amp;rsquo;re out there. I can feel you now. I know that you&amp;rsquo;re afraid&amp;hellip; You&amp;rsquo;re afraid of us. You&amp;rsquo;re afraid of change. I don&amp;rsquo;t know the future. I didn&amp;rsquo;t come here to tell you how this is going to end. I came here to tell you how it&amp;rsquo;s going to begin. I&amp;rsquo;m going to hang up this phone, and then I&amp;rsquo;m going to show these people what you don&amp;rsquo;t want them to see.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
